

Rafid Butt

647-668-0854 rafidbutt12@gmail.com Toronto ON

SUMMARY

Well-organized, reliable and a customer focused individual. Experienced sales associate with strengths in restocking shelves, facing, and customer service. Friendly, knowledgeable and a hard-working team player. Like to work as part of a group while improving my individual skills on the sales floor. Confident when talking to people and a fast learner.

EXPERIENCE

Islamic Institute of Toronto/ Sept 2018 to Mar 2019

Volunteer Toronto, ON

- · Pick up prayer mats and helped clean the mosque.
- · Engaged with others successfully using strong verbal and communication skills.
- Completed assigned duties and consistently produced high volume of work to support daily needs.
- · Kept facilities organized, clean and well-maintained to best meet program needs.

Islamic Institute of Toronto/ Sept 2018 to Feb 2019

Assistant Ball Hockey Coach - Volunteer

Toronto, ON

- Notified head coach of problems with discipline, performance and other decisionmaking areas.
- Motivated and encouraged team members to communicate more openly and constructively with each other.
- Mentored and encouraged youth to develop strong work ethic by being positive role model and practicing skills regularly.
- Planned strategies and selected optimal team lineups to execute game plans.
- Guided athletes with encouragement, motivation and nutritional advice to support athletic performance and overall well-being.

Canadian Tire/ 2017 to 2018

Sales Associate - Seasonal Employment

Burlington, ON

- · Worked for my dad in March break, Winter vacation, etc.
- Helped customers find specific products and answered questions quickly and accurately.
- Stocked shelves and made sure items were not outdated and brought forward.
- Assisted people in different departments to make the process run smoothly
- Cleaned inside and outside the store by picking up garbage and sweeping floors
- Used a walkie talkie when assistance was needed to find a product
- Worked with a team of employees to finish the tasks fast and efficiently

SKILLS

- Excellent communication skills
- Reliable and punctual
- Organizational Skills

- · Listening skills
- · Customer- and service-oriented
- · Work in a fast-paced environment

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Software Engineering Technology Centennial College of Applied Arts And Technology Sept 2020 - Present

High School Diploma Lester B. Pearson Collegiate Institute June 2020